Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Holmes, W.H. (Box 42)
    - To Boas, 1904 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1905 May 29
    - To Boas, 1905 June 2
    - To Boas, 1905 June 14
    - To Boas, 1905 June 21
    - To Boas, 1905 June 22
    - To Boas, 1905 June 22
    - To Boas, 1905 June 22
    - To Boas, 1905 July 7
    - To Boas, 1905 July 28
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 11
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 28
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 13
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1906 May 1
    - To Boas, 1906 June 2
    - To Boas, 1906 June 19
    - To Boas, 1906 July 11
    - To Boas, 1906 July 12
    - To Boas, 1906 July 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 May 8
    - To Boas, 1907 May 9
    - To Boas, 1907 May 24
    - To Boas, 1907 May 25
    - To Boas, 1907 May 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 May 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 May 1
    - To Boas, 1909 May 1
    - To Boas, 1909 June 21
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 13
    - (See Balen, J.C.F. to Andrews, H.A. Feb. 5, 1911), 1913 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 30
    - (Enc. with Holmes, W.H. Oct. 30, 1914), 1914 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Woodworth, R.S., Sept. 2,1931
      - From Holmes to T.S. Dennison, 1909 Dec. 18
      - From Holmes to William Jones, 1905 Oct. 26
      - From Holmes to A.L. Kroeber, 1904 Nov. 1
      - From Holmes to S.P. Langley, 1904 Dec. 3
      - From Holmes to L. de Rouge, 1905 Dec. 14
      - From Holmes to L. de Rouge, 1906 Jan. 17
      - From Holmes to H.H. St. Clair, 1903 July 2
      - From Holmes to Edward Sapir, 1905 June 21
      - From Holmes to Frank G. Speck, 1905 June 22
      - From Holmes to Frank G. Speck, 1905 June 21
      - To Holmes from E. de Rouge, 1905 Dec. 7
      - To Holmes from E. de Rouge, 1906 Jan. 5
      - W.H. Holmes -- to T.F. Ahern, 1904 Dec. 16; 1p.
      - W.H. Holmes -- from H.A. Andrews, 1905 Aug. 16 and 26
      - W.H. Holmes -- from H.A. Andrews, 1906 Jan. 20
      - W.H. Holmes -- to Councillors of the Amer. Anthropological Ass., 1919 Sept. 12; 1p.
      - W.H. Holmes -- from Arbrot? Bacon, 1906 May 18
      - W.H. Holmes -- from J.C.F. Balen, 1911 Feb. 5
      - W.H. Holmes -- from Paul Carus, 1906 May 17
      - W.H. Holmes -- from C.J. Crivelli, 1905 Mar. 20
      - W.H. Holmes -- to J.P. Dunn, 1907 Oct. 21
      - W.H. Holmes -- to J.P. Dunn, 1907 Oct. 26
      - W.H. Holmes -- from J.P. Dunn, 1907 Oct. 24
      - W.H. Holmes -- from J.W. Fewkes, 1914 Nov. 5
      - W.H. Holmes -- from J.W.B. Hewett, 1908 Jan. 29
      - W.H. Holmes -- from Heysinger, 1904 Oct. 26
      - W.H. Holmes -- to F.W. Hodge, 1904 Nov. 7; 1p.
      - W.H. Holmes -- from W.J. McGee, 1910 Jan. 26
      - W.H. Holmes -- from Constance Warren, 1936 Feb. 20
  - Holmes, W.W. (Box 42)
    - W.W. Holmes -- to James Keen McCattell, 1927 Nov. 29; 1p.
  - Holmot, Roger
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p.
  - Holsom (Box 43)
  - Holt, Hamilton (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; telegram
  - Holt, Heery and Co. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1931 May 22; 1p.
  - Holtcena, E.E. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1914 June 1
  - Holtzer, C.W. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec.; 1p.
  - Holtzman, A.M. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 18; 1p.
  - Holz, Cyrus (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 19; 2p.
  - Holzapfel, A.C. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 14; 1p.
  - Holzman, James M. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 9; 1p.
  - Honath, A. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1910 May 11
  - Honey, James A. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1909 June 14; 2p.
  - Honti, J.T. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1933 June 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p.
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 2; 1p.
  - Hooper, F.H. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 23; 2p.
  - Hooper, Franklin W. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1903 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 24
  - Hoops, Johannes (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1923 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 June 13; 5p.
  - Hooton, E.A. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Dec. 8,1916), 1920 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - (See note on Boas, F. to Hrdlicks, A. Nov. 6, 1932), 1936 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 21 and May 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 28; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 29; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec.; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - Enc. with Boas, F. to Shotwell, J.T., Apr. 20, 1942.
    - See Shotwell, J.T., Apr. 21, 1942.
    - E.A. Hooton -- to G.H. Estabrooks, 1926 Oct. 21
    - (Enc. originally with Estabrooks, G.H., Oct. 26, 1926)
    - E.A. Hooton -- from G.H. Estabrooks, 1926 Oct. 26
    - (Enc. originally with Estabrooks, G.H., Oct. 26, 1926)
    - E.A. Hooton -- to A. Hrdlicka, 1924 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally in Hrdlicka, A., Dec. 16,1924)
    - E.A. Hooton -- from Frederic T. Lewis, 1937 Sept. 25
    - E.A. Hooton -- from T.W. Todd, 1935 Nov. 2
  - Hoover, Herbert C. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 2p.
  - Hopfer (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - (See Boas, F. to Engerrand, G.C., Oct. 31,1913)
  - Hopifred (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1913 May 29; 2p.
  - Hopkins, E.M. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 15; 1p.
  - Hopkins, E.W. (Box 43)
    - E.W. Hopkins -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Apr. 3
  - Hopkins, J.A.H. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 4; 2p.
  - Hoppe, Hans (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1932 May 29; bill
  - Hoppenstedt, G.L. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 12
  - Hoppmann, K. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1935 May 14; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Bonhage, M., May 21, 1935)
    - K. Hoppmann -- from M. Bonhage, 1935 May 21
    - (Enc. with Bonhage, M., May 21, 1935)
  - Horace Mann School (Box 43)
    See Reynolds, R.G.
  - Horch, L.L. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 18; 1p.
  - Hori, Keutok (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 3
  - Horn, Beatrice (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 14; 2p.
      (Enc: Draft of prospectus)
  - Horn, E. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 15; 2p.
  - Horn, Walter (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 7; 1p.
  - Hornbostel, E.M. von (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 July 13
    - From Boas, 1920 May 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 July 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Boas, F. to Gregory, H.E. July 23, 1929), 1929 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 28; 2p.
  - Hornbostel, Henry (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1910 May 23
  - Hornbostel, J. von (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 31; 2p.
  - Horowitz, Marvin (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 30; 1p.
  - Horsefield, R.B. (Box 43)
    - R.B. Horsefield -- to Editor, Nat. Hist. Dept. Family The Pas, Manitoba Herald, 1933 Jan. 22; 4p.
  - Horsford, Cornelia (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1894 Sept. 6
    - To Boas, 1894 July 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1894 July 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Sept. 10; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1896 May 25
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 May 27; 2p.
  - Hortelit? A? (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 12; 2p.
  - Horton, Donald (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 8; 2p.
  - Horton, E.A. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 15
  - Hoskins, J. Preston (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 30; 2p.
  - Hostos, A. de (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 20; 2p.
  - Hotelling, H. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 20; 1p.
  - Hotesch (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 12; 1p.
  - Hotzsch, Otto (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 12; 3p.
  - Hough, F.H. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 23
  - Hough, W. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - (See Boas, F. to Gordon, G.B. May 22, 1916), 1916 Dec. 8
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Dec. 8, 1916), 1918 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 20; 1p.
  - H.O. Houghton & Co. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 6
    - From Boas, 1909 May 8
    - From Boas, 1909 May 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 20
    - H.O. Houghton & Co. -- to Mrs. E. Krackwitzer, undated; 1p.
  - Houghton, H.P. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 30; 1p.
  - Houghton, L.S. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 10
  - Houghton, Mifflin & Co. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 14; 1p.
      (Enc: Publisher's note to American version of Hitler's "My Battle".)
  - Houle, J.L. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 20; 2p.
  - Hourwich, I.A. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 26; 1p.
  - House, R.T. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 21; 1p.
  - Houston, S.F. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 3
  - Hovey, E.O. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 23; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 21
    - E.O. Hovey -- to H.A. Andrews, 1909 Dec. 16
    - E.O. Hovey -- to R. MacDougall, 1907 Oct. 8
    - E.O. Hovey -- from Emerson McMillin, 1913 Nov. 10
  - Howard, Alice M. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
  - Howard, Edgar B. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 9; 1p.
  - Howard, F.T. (Box 43)
    - See Boas, F. to Wright, E.H., Mar. 16, 1931.
  - Howard, H.S. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p.
  - Howard, Leland Ossiar (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 1p.
  - Howard, William E. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
  - Howard University (Box 43)
    See Johnson, Mordecai W.
    See Scott, Emmett J.
  - Howe, A.D. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 23; 1p.
  - Howe, F.C. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 17; 1p.
  - Howe, George P. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1911 May 13
    - From Boas, 1911 May 18
    - To Boas, 1911 May 11
    - To Boas, 1911 May 16
  - Howe, J. Morgan (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 May 30; 2p.
  - Howe, L.M. (Box 43)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 30; 1p.
  - Howe, Lavinia V. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 23; 2p.
  - Howe, Marshall A. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 15; 1p.
    - M.A. Howe -- from J.A.B. Nolla, 1935 Apr. 23; 1p.
  - Howe, Quincy (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 14; 1p.
  - Howell, M.D. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 3; 1p.
  - Howell, W.H. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 22; 1p.
  - Howells, John N.M. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 10; 2p.
  - Howk, Horace J. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 12; 1p.
  - Howson, Roger (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p.
    - R. Howson -- to E.P. Boas, 1942 Dec. 23; 2p.
  - Hoyt, H. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 23; 2p.
  - Hranilovic, H. von (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 17; 3p.
  - Hrdlicka, A. (Box 43)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - (See Boas, F. to Gordon, G.B. May22,1916), 1916 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Dec. 8,1916), 1917 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 23; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 June 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc: See Boas, F. to Hrdlicka, A. Mar. 13, 1919), 1919 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 24; 1p.
    - (Enc: Boas, F. to Yves-Guyot, Director Ecole d'anthropologie re International institute of anthropology, Dec. 31, 1918), 1919 Sept. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 25; 1p.
      (Note: Reply written below)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 June; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; telegram
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 7; 1p.